A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1984-1994, 2004-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1984-1994, 2006.
  - 2005 (Accession 44118)., 9 cu. ft. (9 boxes)
    - SUSTA, 2005. (Box 6)
    - Suggested Response (5), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Suggested Response (4), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Suggested Response (3), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Suggested Response (2), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Suggested Response (1), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Dairy Regulation Tracking letters (1), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Dairy Regulation Tracking letters (2), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Dairy Regulation Tracking letters (3), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Dairy Regulation Tracking letters (4), 2005. (Box 6)
    - Census of Agriculture brochure, 2005. (Box 7)
    - Due Diligence Plan, 2005. (Box 7)
    - PPEA Enterprise Applications Steering Committee, 2005. (Box 7)
    - Enterprise Applications Project (1), 2005. (Box 7)
    - Enterprise Applications Project (2), 2005. (Box 7)
    - Legislative Files, 2005. (Box 8)
    - Executive Orders, 1998-2002. (Box 8)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee Meeting, 2005 Dec 14. (Box 9)
    - Consumer Affiars Advisory Committe, 2005. (Box 9)
    - Service Award Ceremonies, 2005. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board of Directors meeting, 2005 Dec 6. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation Annual Convention, 2005 Nov 28-29. (Box 9)
    - Eastern Shore Conference, 2005 Jan 4-5. (Box 9)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association Board of Director's meeting, 2005 Jan 19. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board meeting, 2005 Jan 20. (Box 9)
    - VACPA annual meeting, 2005 Jan 25. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Pork Industry Conference, 2005 Jan 26. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Grown Conference and Trade Show, 2005 Jan 27-28. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Soybean Association Winter Conference, 2005 Feb 4. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Cotton meeting, 2005 Feb 9. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Agricultural Summit, 2005 Feb 21-22. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Wine Board meeting, 2005 Mar 30. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Agricultural Council Board meeting, 2005 Mar 28. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board of Directors meeting, 2005 Mar 24. (Box 9)
    - VEIAA breakfast, 2005 Mar 23. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Food and Beverage Association meeting, 2005 Mar 24. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Beef Industry Convention, 2005 Feb 24-26. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Public Service Week, 2005 May 2-8. (Box 9)
    - Developing Your Public Sector Balance Scorecard, 2005 May 4. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Arbor Day ceremony, 2005 Apr 29. (Box 9)
    - Pesticide Control Board meeting, 2005 Apr 21. (Box 9)
    - VFBF Emerging Agriculture Enterprises Ad-Hoc Committee meeting, 2005 Apr 18. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Beef Expo, 2005 Apr 15. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Poultry Health and Management Seminar, 2005 Apr 12-13. (Box 9)
    - Southern Crop Production Association meeting, 2005 Oct 18-19. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Sustainable Future Summit, 2005 Sept 13-15. (Box 9)
    - Agriculture Field Day, 2005 Aug 23. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Agricultural Expo, 2005 Aug 11. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation meeting, 2005 June 26. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board meeting, 2005 July 21. (Box 9)
    - VEIAA Conference, 2005 June 22-23. (Box 9)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board meeting, 2005 Oct 20. (Box 9)
    - Continuity of Operations, 2005 Jan. (Box 9)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services meeting, 2005 Dec 8. (Box 9)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services meeting, 2005 Sept 23. (Box 9)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services meeting, 2005 July 13. (Box 9)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services meeting, 2005 Mar 17. (Box 9)
  - 2006 (Accession 44828)., 8 cu. ft. (8 boxes)
    - Weekly reports to the Secretary, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Blankenship, Donald (Deputy Commissioner), 2006 Nov-Dec. (Box 1)
    - Blankenship, Donald (Deputy Commissioner), 2006 Jan-Nov. (Box 1)
    - Memos (SMT), 2006. (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous - Commissioner's Office, 2006.
    - Miscellaneous - Administrative and Finance Services, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Adams, Sandra, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Harris, Larry, 2006.
    - Miscellaneous - Facility Management, 2006. (Box 1)
    - Halblieb, Craig, 2006 Sept-Dec.
    - Halblieb, Craig, 2006 June-Aug. (Box 1)
    - Halblieb, Craig, 2006 Jan-May. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Kapelewski, Joseph - Finance Office, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Layman, Barbara, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Development Services, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Dickenson, William P., Jr., 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal and Food Industry Services, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Wilkes, Richard, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Dairy and Food Security, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Food Uniformity Act, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Office of Dairy and Foods, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Promotions, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Lidholm, Elaine, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (CAAC), 2006. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Alvarez, Andy, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Office of Consumer Affairs, 2006. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 Sept-Nov. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 June-Oct. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 Mar-June. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 2006 Jan-Mar. (Box 3)
    - Office of Plants and Pest Services, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Bee Keeping study, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Report on Weights and Measures Fees, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Office of Product and Industry Standards, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Butts, Donald, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Human Resources Office, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Jackson, Karen E., 2006. (Box 3)
    - Audit - Seed Laboratory, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Martin, Jay - Internal Auditor, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Seward, Roy, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy Planning and Research, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Stewardship, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Giles, Perida, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Askew, Rebecca, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Sleight, Thomas, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Office of International Marketing, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Accomplishments - Governor, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Agendas (SMT), 2006. (Box 3)
    - Agreement - Farmers Markets Nutrition Program, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Coop Agreement - VDACS and USDA, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Apple Board, Virginia, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Attorney General, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Audit FLSA, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Avian Influenza, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Boll Weevil, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Boll -Weevil - Eradication Foundation, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Chipokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Virginia Agricultural Foundation, 2006. (Box 3)
    - CVC, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 2006. (Box 3)
    - Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Comptroller's Office, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Consolidated Lab Services, Div. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Cooperative Coyote Damage Control Program Report, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Cotton Board, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Delegates, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Disaster, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Economic Impact of Agriculture Report, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Education, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Contacts, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Evacuation Plan, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - EPA, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Farmers Market Board, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Foundation for Virginia's Natural Resources Board, 2006. (Box 4)
    - FOIA, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Govenor's Office, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Grant awards, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Health, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Horse Center, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - House Bill 980, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Interior, U.S. Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, 2006. (Box 4)
    - VITA, 2006. (Box 4)
    - JLARC Study, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Katrina Analysis, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Land Use, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Mandates - Federal, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Organic Milk Study, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Milk Commission, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Mountain View Farms, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Moving Relocation Expenses, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Peanut Growers Association, Virginia, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Performance Measures, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Plasticulture, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Referendum - Cotton, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Referendum on levy - equine feed, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Risk Management Division (DGS), 2006. (Box 4)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Senators, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Sole Source, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Solem, Christine (goat milk), 2006. (Box 4)
    - Soutern States, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Specialty Crop Block Grant Program, 2006. (Box 4)
    - State Police, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - State Fair, 2006. (Box 4)
    - State Ratification Committee, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Strategic Planning, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Strategic Plan, 2005-2006. (Box 4)
    - Taxation, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Telecommuting, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Tobacco, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2006. (Box 4)
    - Transportation, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 4)
    - USDA, 2006 Oct-Dec. (Box 4)
    - Out of Country requests, 2006. (Box 5)
    - Telecommunications bill, 2006. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 Sept-Oct. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 July-Aug. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 May-June. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 March-April. (Box 5)
    - Reader File, 2006 Jan-Feb. (Box 5)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board - Meeting, 2006 Sept. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Food and Beverage Association Fall Education Conference, 2006 Sept. (Box 6)
    - Agiculture and Consumer Services Board - Meeting, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Agriculture Field Day, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Nursery and Landscape Association Field Day, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - State Fair - Virginia Wine Competition Luncheon, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agriculture Expo, 2006 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Virginia State Dairymen's Association Board - Meeting, 2006 July. (Box 6)
    - Hurricane Emergency Exercise, 2006 July. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 July. (Box 6)
    - Commercial Vegetable Production Field Day, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Northampton County Agriculture Tour, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Innovations in Government Conference, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board - Meeting, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Simply Fresh opening, 2006 June. (Box 6)
    - Agriculture and Consumer Service Board - Meeting, 2006 May. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Health and Management Seminar, 2006 Apr. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Beef Expo, 2006 Apr. (Box 6)
    - Seminar - Assist Producers in Marketing Virginia Meat Products, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council - Meeting, 2006 mar. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Animal ID Forum, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation Board - Meeting, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Wine Board - Meeting, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Emergency Management Celebration and Open House, 2006 Mar. (Box 6)
    - Emergency Operations Training, 2006 Feb. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Corn Growers Association and Virginia Soybean Association - Meeting, 2006 Feb. (Box 6)
    - VITA - Meeting, 2006 Feb. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Grown Conference, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Pork Conference, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Crop Production Association, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Dairymen's Association Board - Meeting, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - Eastern Shore Agriculture Conference and Trade Show, 2006 Jan. (Box 6)
    - AFIS, 2006. (Box 6)
    - CP, 2006. (Box 6)
    - CP Completed, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Marketing, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Marketing Completed, 2006. (Box 6)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Sept-Oct. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 July-Aug. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 May-June. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Mar-May. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Feb-Mar. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006 Jan. (Box 7)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 2006. (Box 7)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee - Meeting, 2006 May. (Box 7)
    - Post General Assembly Session Analysis and Review, 2006 May. (Box 7)
    - Public Service Week, 2006 May. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Arbor Day Ceremony, 2006 Apr. (Box 7)
    - Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 Apr. (Box 7)
    - Environment Virginia Symposium, 2006 Apr. (Box 7)
    - State Service Merit Awards Presentations, 2006. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Agribus Council - Meetings, 2006 Nov. (Box 7)
    - CMA-VEIAA - Meeting, 2006 Nov. (Box 7)
    - Tomatoes and Food Safety - Meeting, 2006 Nov. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Wine Appreciation Celebration, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Senate Committee on Agriculture, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Conservation of Natural Resources, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Emergency Management - AI Exercise, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Agriculture Summit, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board - Meeting, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - Virginia Energy Conference, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
    - USDA, 2006 Jan-Sept. (Box 8)
    - U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service grant, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Veterans Services, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU), 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Executive Institute (VEI), 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Tech (VPISU), 2006. (Box 8)
    - Year End Closure, 2006. (Box 8)
    - YMCA, 2006. (Box 8)
    - NASDA, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Virginia Wine Board, 2006. (Box 8)
    - Suggested Responses, 2006 Sept-Dec. (Box 8)
    - Suggested Responses, 2006 May-Sept. (Box 8)
    - Suggested Responses, 2006 Jan-May. (Box 8)